<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title><![CDATA[The Aurelia Blog]]></title>
    <link>http://aurelia.io/blog</link>
    <description><![CDATA[The official blog of the Aurelia project and Core Team.]]></description>
    <generator>Aurelia Docs</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun Aug 19 2018 21:08:36 GMT-0700 (PDT)</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[CoinMesh brings Litecoin and Bitcoin dApp development to Aurelia developers]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2018/08/19/coinmesh-litecoin-bitcoin-aurelia-dapps</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Today, we're thrilled to invite former core team member and long-time Aurelia community member, Patrick Walters, to share a special announcement regarding the exciting, new project he's been working on. Let's hear what Patrick has been up to...]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun Aug 19 2018 21:08:35 GMT-0700 (PDT)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia vNext]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2018/08/05/aurelia-vnext</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The codebase of today's Aurelia is approaching 4 years old. Much has changed in the industry since 2014, with advances in JavaScript, TypeScript, module loading, packaging, browsers, tooling, and much more. We've worked hard over the years to maintain full backwards compatibility and minimal-to-no breaking changes. We're one of the only frameworks that has managed to achieve this. Most other frameworks have several major breaking change releases every year. Aurelia's stability is something we know our community appreciates, and it's something we're very proud of. That said, it has been almost four years and the time has finally come to think about Aurelia's next major version.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun Aug 05 2018 21:18:48 GMT-0700 (PDT)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia 2018 Q2 Report]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2018/08/05/aurelia-2018-q2-report</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The second quarter of 2018 was an amazing time for the Aurelia team with some major progress towards key goals in our 2018 roadmap [blog/2018/01/03/aurelia-2018-roadmap/]. Read on to hear about what we've accomplished and what's in store next.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun Aug 05 2018 21:18:26 GMT-0700 (PDT)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia Release Notes - Late July 2018]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2018/07/24/aurelia-release-notes-late-july-2018</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This month we've a fixed number of issues in the routing and templating engines, including a few regressions that cropped up in the previous round of releases. Additionally, we've moved the aurelia-dialog plugin to a 1.0.0 release and have begun work on 2.0.0.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue Jul 24 2018 21:21:54 GMT-0700 (PDT)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia Release Notes - June 2018]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2018/06/24/aurelia-release-notes-june-2018</link>
      <description><![CDATA[June is a significant month for Aurelia. Our latest set of releases adds some great new features for our templating engine, allowing more seamless Webpack builds and an even more unobtrusive programming model. We've also made huge improvements to our binding engine, including adding new keywords and beefing up performance. Finally, the Aurelia Store plugin was released! Read on to get the details from the Aurelia Core Team.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun Jun 24 2018 23:03:59 GMT-0700 (PDT)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia Store Released!]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2018/06/17/aurelia-store-released</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Announcing the release of the Aurelia Store state management plugin!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun Jun 17 2018 23:28:50 GMT-0700 (PDT)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Financing Changes to Aurelia]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2018/05/16/financing-changes-to-aurelia</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Announcing some major changes to Aurelia's financial ecosystem that will accelerate the future of the Aurelia framework.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed May 16 2018 21:15:12 GMT-0700 (PDT)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia Release Notes - Early May 2018]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2018/05/10/aurelia-release-notes-early-may-2018</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We're excited to be working on a number of great new improvements to Aurelia's templating and binding engines. Just this week we've released the first set of improvements to the binding engine, which merge the Lexer and the Parser. By doing this we were able to increase the performance of binding parsing by 10x in some cases!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu May 10 2018 23:34:44 GMT-0700 (PDT)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Visual Studio Code Extension 1.0.0 Release]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2018/04/09/visual-studio-code-extension-100-release</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the latest release of the Visual Studio code extension from 0.3.4 to 1.0.0 we removed the preview tag and moved to a stable version.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon Apr 09 2018 07:13:01 GMT-0700 (PDT)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia RealWorld App]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2018/04/04/aurelia-realworld-app</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thanks to the fantastic work of Moritz Hilberg and other community members, Aurelia is now available as part of the RealWorld project [https://github.com/gothinkster/realworld]. Here's Moritz to tell you more about it...]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed Apr 04 2018 20:32:01 GMT-0700 (PDT)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia 2018 Q1 Report]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2018/04/02/aurelia-2018-q1-report</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the first quarter of 2018 now behind us, we wanted to take the time to provide an update on the progress the Aurelia team and community have made towards our 2018 roadmap goals [blog/2018/01/03/aurelia-2018-roadmap].]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon Apr 02 2018 07:10:40 GMT-0700 (PDT)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia Release Notes - Late March 2018]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2018/03/29/aurelia-release-notes-late-march-2018</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We're excited to share that we've recently published a new version of the Aurelia CLI which is packed with bug fixes and new features.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu Mar 29 2018 12:14:37 GMT-0700 (PDT)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Practical App Development with Aurelia]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2018/03/26/practical-app-development-with-aurelia</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This week we welcome Matt Duffield to tell us about his new Aurelia book!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon Mar 26 2018 19:52:11 GMT-0700 (PDT)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Building Office 365/SharePoint Applications with Aurelia]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2018/03/21/building-office-365sharepoint-applications-with-aurelia</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This week, please welcome community member Magnus Danielson to share a little bit about Aurelia and Office 365. Take it away Magnus!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed Mar 21 2018 11:41:22 GMT-0700 (PDT)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia Release Notes - Early March 2018]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2018/03/04/aurelia-release-notes-early-march-2018</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Last week we announced official support for Server-Side Rendering in Aurelia [blog/2018/02/25/server-side-rendering]. This week we're announcing an update to our Webpack tooling to support Webpack 4.0! We've also got a number of incremental fixes and small new features for other Aurelia libraries, detailed below.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun Mar 04 2018 22:40:38 GMT-0800 (PST)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Server Side Rendering]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2018/02/25/server-side-rendering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Without Server Side Rendering the server returns only boilerplate HTML without any content. Today we're announcing Aurelia Server Side Rendering which allows a Node.js server to render your application on the server and return the HTML of a fully rendered page.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun Feb 25 2018 22:36:44 GMT-0800 (PST)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[AureliaCasts - Creating Compelling Aurelia Video Tutorials]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2018/02/15/aureliacasts-creating-compelling-aurelia-video-tutorials</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This week, we're proud to have community member and creator of AureliaCasts, Nick Shallee, guest posting to share with our community what he's been up to.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu Feb 15 2018 22:00:06 GMT-0800 (PST)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia Users Community Space Guides]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2018/02/11/aurelia-users-community-space-guides</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Today, I'd like to invite a long-time Aurelia Community Member, Nikolaj Ivancic, to share a little bit about the "AUCS" community project that he's leading to help improve Aurelia's documentation. Take it away Nik!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun Feb 11 2018 21:18:48 GMT-0800 (PST)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia Release Notes - Early February 2018]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2018/02/05/aurelia-release-notes-early-february-2018</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continuing into 2018, we've got a number of fixes and improvements to core Aurelia libraries and plugins. The details are available below.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon Feb 05 2018 01:29:20 GMT-0800 (PST)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Big Changes in the Aurelia Router 1.5.0 Release]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2018/01/22/big-changes-in-the-aurelia-router-150-release</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thanks to the new features in the latest update to the Aurelia router, building a beautiful and functional master-detail page in Aurelia is quick and easy.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon Jan 22 2018 01:19:46 GMT-0800 (PST)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia 2018 Roadmap]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2018/01/03/aurelia-2018-roadmap</link>
      <description><![CDATA[2017 was a great year for Aurelia but 2018 is shaping up to be even better!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed Jan 03 2018 10:02:07 GMT-0800 (PST)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia Release Notes - December 2017]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2017/12/20/aurelia-release-notes-december-2017</link>
      <description><![CDATA[2017 is almost at an end. So, we wanted to close out this year with another set of releases to Aurelia, its plugins and tools. Below you can read the details on the bug fixes, performance improvements and new features available in the latest libraries.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed Dec 20 2017 11:20:01 GMT-0800 (PST)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia OpenID Connect]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2017/12/13/aurelia-openid-connect</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This week we invite Aurelia community member, Shaun Luttin [https://github.com/shaunluttin], to share with us a bit about the Aurelia OpenID connect plugin he's been working on. Take it away Shaun...]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed Dec 13 2017 23:16:31 GMT-0800 (PST)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia Framework7]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2017/12/03/aurelia-framework7</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thanks to the investigative work of one of our community members, Andy [https://github.com/weoreference], we've got another great Aurelia component framework to share with you: Aurelia-Framework7. Read on to learn more, directly from Alexander Flenniken [https://github.com/alflennik], the creator of this project...]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun Dec 03 2017 21:11:31 GMT-0800 (PST)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia UX Overhaul]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2017/11/15/aurelia-ux-overhaul</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We've been doing some major work on Aurelia UX, both in terms of building out components and refining the core capabilities and approach. In this post, we'd like to share a bit about the details of our most recent set of releases.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed Nov 15 2017 10:50:44 GMT-0800 (PST)</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
