<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title><![CDATA[The Aurelia Blog]]></title>
    <link>http://aurelia.io/blog</link>
    <description><![CDATA[The official blog of the Aurelia project and Core Team.]]></description>
    <generator>Aurelia Docs</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu Mar 29 2018 12:14:38 GMT-0700 (PDT)</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia Release Notes - Late March 2018]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2018/03/29/aurelia-release-notes-late-march-2018</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We're excited to share that we've recently published a new version of the Aurelia CLI which is packed with bug fixes and new features.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu Mar 29 2018 12:14:37 GMT-0700 (PDT)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Practical App Development with Aurelia]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2018/03/26/practical-app-development-with-aurelia</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This week we welcome Matt Duffield to tell us about his new Aurelia book!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon Mar 26 2018 19:52:11 GMT-0700 (PDT)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Building Office 365/SharePoint Applications with Aurelia]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2018/03/21/building-office-365sharepoint-applications-with-aurelia</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This week, please welcome community member Magnus Danielson to share a little bit about Aurelia and Office 365. Take it away Magnus!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed Mar 21 2018 11:41:22 GMT-0700 (PDT)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia Release Notes - Early March 2018]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2018/03/04/aurelia-release-notes-early-march-2018</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Last week we announced official support for Server-Side Rendering in Aurelia [blog/2018/02/25/server-side-rendering]. This week we're announcing an update to our Webpack tooling to support Webpack 4.0! We've also got a number of incremental fixes and small new features for other Aurelia libraries, detailed below.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun Mar 04 2018 22:40:38 GMT-0800 (PST)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Server Side Rendering]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2018/02/25/server-side-rendering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Without Server Side Rendering the server returns only boilerplate HTML without any content. Today we're announcing Aurelia Server Side Rendering which allows a Node.js server to render your application on the server and return the HTML of a fully rendered page.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun Feb 25 2018 22:36:44 GMT-0800 (PST)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[AureliaCasts - Creating Compelling Aurelia Video Tutorials]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2018/02/15/aureliacasts-creating-compelling-aurelia-video-tutorials</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This week, we're proud to have community member and creator of AureliaCasts, Nick Shallee, guest posting to share with our community what he's been up to.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu Feb 15 2018 22:00:06 GMT-0800 (PST)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia Users Community Space Guides]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2018/02/11/aurelia-users-community-space-guides</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Today, I'd like to invite a long-time Aurelia Community Member, Nikolaj Ivancic, to share a little bit about the "AUCS" community project that he's leading to help improve Aurelia's documentation. Take it away Nik!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun Feb 11 2018 21:18:48 GMT-0800 (PST)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia Release Notes - Early February 2018]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2018/02/05/aurelia-release-notes-early-february-2018</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continuing into 2018, we've got a number of fixes and improvements to core Aurelia libraries and plugins. The details are available below.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon Feb 05 2018 01:29:20 GMT-0800 (PST)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Big Changes in the Aurelia Router 1.5.0 Release]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2018/01/22/big-changes-in-the-aurelia-router-150-release</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thanks to the new features in the latest update to the Aurelia router, building a beautiful and functional master-detail page in Aurelia is quick and easy.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon Jan 22 2018 01:19:46 GMT-0800 (PST)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia 2018 Roadmap]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2018/01/03/aurelia-2018-roadmap</link>
      <description><![CDATA[2017 was a great year for Aurelia but 2018 is shaping up to be even better!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed Jan 03 2018 10:02:07 GMT-0800 (PST)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia Release Notes - December 2017]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2017/12/20/aurelia-release-notes-december-2017</link>
      <description><![CDATA[2017 is almost at an end. So, we wanted to close out this year with another set of releases to Aurelia, its plugins and tools. Below you can read the details on the bug fixes, performance improvements and new features available in the latest libraries.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed Dec 20 2017 11:20:01 GMT-0800 (PST)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia OpenID Connect]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2017/12/13/aurelia-openid-connect</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This week we invite Aurelia community member, Shaun Luttin [https://github.com/shaunluttin], to share with us a bit about the Aurelia OpenID connect plugin he's been working on. Take it away Shaun...]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed Dec 13 2017 23:16:31 GMT-0800 (PST)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia Framework7]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2017/12/03/aurelia-framework7</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thanks to the investigative work of one of our community members, Andy [https://github.com/weoreference], we've got another great Aurelia component framework to share with you: Aurelia-Framework7. Read on to learn more, directly from Alexander Flenniken [https://github.com/alflennik], the creator of this project...]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun Dec 03 2017 21:11:31 GMT-0800 (PST)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia UX Overhaul]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2017/11/15/aurelia-ux-overhaul</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We've been doing some major work on Aurelia UX, both in terms of building out components and refining the core capabilities and approach. In this post, we'd like to share a bit about the details of our most recent set of releases.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed Nov 15 2017 10:50:44 GMT-0800 (PST)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Projects That Make Aurelia Shine]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2017/11/12/projects-that-make-aurelia-shine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This week, Aurelia community member and author, Sean Hunter, shares a section from his book "Aurelia in Action".]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun Nov 12 2017 23:30:29 GMT-0800 (PST)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia Release Notes - Early November 2017]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2017/11/10/aurelia-release-notes-early-november-2017</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As always, the Aurelia Team continues to fix bugs, add new features and make tons of improvements throughout the framework. In this set of releases, we've got a minor breaking change to our dialog plugin. We've also converted our testing library to TypeScript. While we've made no changes to the API or behavior, we've bumped the major version since the improved, more-accurate typings may affect some TypeScript users. Finally, we've launched another major set of enhancements to the CLI and made our initial launch of the HTTP Mocking library. Huge thanks to Thomas Schlage [https://github.com/fragsalat] for his work on the new library.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri Nov 10 2017 11:54:29 GMT-0800 (PST)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Announcing the Aurelia Discourse and New Site Experience!]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2017/10/23/aurelia-discourse-and-new-site-experience</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Today, we're thrilled to announce that we've launched the official Aurelia Discourse forum [https://discourse.aurelia.io]! At the same time, we've completely overhauled our site [http://aurelia.io/] and documentation technology, opening the way for better docs and learning to come.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon Oct 23 2017 00:28:28 GMT-0700 (PDT)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia at Techdays The Netherlands]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2017/10/10/aurelia-at-techdays-the-netherlands</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Techdays The Netherlands is just two days away! There's some great Aurelia content for you, if you are attending this event. Read on to learn more about the upcoming talks.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue Oct 10 2017 08:45:58 GMT-0700 (PDT)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia Release Notes - Early October 2017]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2017/10/03/aurelia-release-notes-early-october-2017</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We've just made a massive set of releases to Aurelia's core libraries and plugins. This set of releases includes perf optimizations, reduced memory utilization, removal of a memory leak, plenty of fixed bugs and adds some new features!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue Oct 03 2017 08:36:23 GMT-0700 (PDT)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Case Study: Ivee 3D Editor - Aurelia+Azure+ASP.NET+Redux+ThreeJS]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2017/09/26/ivee-3d-editor-aurelia-microsoft-azure-case-study</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Today, I'm pleased to introduce you to Daniel Radu. Dan is a member of our Aurelia community who has been building some pretty awesome stuff by combining Aurelia [http://aurelia.io] with Microsoft Azure [https://azure.microsoft.com]. I'll let Dan tell you about his experiences, in his own words...]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue Sep 26 2017 08:59:48 GMT-0700 (PDT)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia Release Notes - Late August 2017]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2017/08/30/aurelia-release-notes-late-august-2017</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We've got a number of bug fixes, enhancements and perf improvements this time around. In particular, we've made some substantial fixes to our CLI Webpack support.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed Aug 30 2017 10:42:22 GMT-0700 (PDT)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia CLI Webpack Update!]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2017/08/18/aurelia-cli-webpack-update</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Today, I'm thrilled to announce that we've added support for Webpack 3 to the Aurelia CLI. With this addition, the CLI supports project generation equally for Webpack, SystemJS and RequireJS.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri Aug 18 2017 06:45:57 GMT-0700 (PDT)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia Release Notes - Mid August 2017]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2017/08/14/aurelia-release-notes-mid-august-2017</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Today, we have a small set of release to update you with. We're gearing up for some big releases next. Stay tuned for more...]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon Aug 14 2017 07:42:42 GMT-0700 (PDT)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Introducing Aurelia in Action]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2017/07/13/introducing-aurelia-in-action</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Aurelia in Action [https://www.manning.com/books/aurelia-in-action] is a book targeted at teaching you what you need to build compelling, real-world applications in Aurelia from the ground up. The book centres around a fictional virtual bookshelf application (similar to Goodreads.com [https://www.goodreads.com/]) called my-books. We start off by creating a bare-bones application via the Aurelia CLI, then progressively layer on various features that users would want in a virtual bookshelf. By the end of the book we've built out a fully fledged SPA, giving you the chance to familiarise yourself with the many tools available in Aurelia's tool-belt along the way. Save 45% off Aurelia in Action [https://www.manning.com/books/aurelia-in-action] with discount code aureliash at Manning.com [https://www.manning.com/] today!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu Jul 13 2017 08:09:39 GMT-0700 (PDT)</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Aurelia Release Notes - Early July 2017]]></title>
      <link>http://aurelia.io/blog/2017/07/07/aurelia-release-notes-early-july-2017</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Aurelia Team continues to iterate and improve all aspects of the framework. Below you can find details on our recent minor release of aurelia-validation along with our patch releases of the aurelia-cli and aurelia-polyfills.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri Jul 07 2017 07:05:30 GMT-0700 (PDT)</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
